​​​ ​♫ Old fortune teller ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ Gave me playing cards, ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ And eight clones appeared in this world, ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ And every one of them is different, ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ All different colors,♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ All different views ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ On all sorts of stuff ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ Who’s the king, and who’s the jack, ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ No two of them are alike ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ What could go wrong? ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫Everything went wrong! ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​What happened… this time?​ ​​
​​​ ​ (Everyone talksover each other)​ ​​
​​​ ​Time out. One by one!​ ​​
​​​ ​It was a wonderful day!​ ​​
​​​ ​Innocent as a dove, I walked into the kitchen to quench my thirst with…​ ​​
​​​ ​a glass of juice.​ ​​
​​​ ​With no ulterior motive!​ ​​
​​​ ​As I began to pour the juice…​ ​​
​​​ ​A teeny tiny little drop spilled on the table. Oops!​ ​​
​​​ ​AAAHHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanted to wipe it off immediately,​ ​​
​​​ ​but…​ ​​
​​​ ​YOUUUUUU!​ ​​
​​​ ​YOU!​ ​​
​​​ ​YOU DIDN’T SWITCH OUT THE SHOWER HEADS!​ ​​
​​​ ​NOW EVERYONE WILL THINK I’M YELLOW BECAUSE I PEED MYSELF!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ew, that’s disgusting.​ ​​
​​​ ​I never said that!​ ​​
​​​ ​What is this?!​ ​​
​​​ ​YOU SPILLED THE JUICE?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now we cannot use this table!​ ​​
​​​ ​You are causing global warming!!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​How?! What are you on about?!​ ​​
​​​ ​…I was just saying!​ ​​
​​​ ​You should’ve seen how he was pouring the juice!​ ​​
​​​ ​(singing nonsense)​ ​​
​​​ ​I’ve heard enough, who’s next?​ ​​
​​​ ​As usual, I was bettering myself as a person,​ ​​
​​​ ​reading about how to keep one’s body in good shape, and came across an article about salt baths.​ ​​
​​​ ​While I was looking for salt,​ ​​
​​​ ​I saw soup sitting on the stove.​ ​​
​​​ ​It looked plain, bland…​ ​​
​​​ ​As a TRUE connoisseur, I simply couldn’t walk by!​ ​​
​​​ ​Since when did you become a connoisseur?​ ​​
​​​ ​Since he started watching the cooking channel.​ ​​
​​​ ​Some tomatoes for the color,​ ​​
​​​ ​lemons for a twinge of sourness,​ ​​
​​​ ​honey for some sweetness, and gorgonzola...​ ​​
​​​ ​for refinement!​ ​​
​​​ ​Where did you get gorgonzola from?!​ ​​
​​​ ​We’ve never had any!..​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh… Are you sure…?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahem… If you say so…​ ​​
​​​ ​What next?​ ​​
​​​ ​Who chops like that!?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let me!​ ​​
​​​ ​(Romeo squeals)​ ​​
​​​ ​Done.​ ​​
​​​ ​YOU IDIOT SANDWICH!​ ​​
​​​ ​A RAT WAS HELPING HIM ALL ALONG!​ ​​
​​​ ​(Heart-rending screams)​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, sorry.​ ​​
​​​ ​(Romeo breathes a sigh of relief)​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​(giggling)​ ​​
​​​ ​Not bad.​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mhm! Perfect!​ ​​
​​​ ​What the heck.​ ​​
​​​ ​AAAHHHH!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Haha!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey! You have to buy a ticket.​ ​​
​​​ ​We don’t have any money.​ ​​
​​​ ​How absurd…​ ​​
​​​ ​I like it.​ ​​
​​​ ​I’m imagining it in the style of…​ ​​
​​​ ​anime!​ ​​
​​​ ​Spaaade!​ ​​
​​​ ​Come over here, you damn tin man!​ ​​
​​​ ​Waruuuu!​ ​​
​​ ​Spaaade!​ ​​
​​​ ​Come over here, you damn tin man!​ ​​
​​​ ​Waruuuu!​ ​​
​​​ ​Who are you calling a tin man, you cr…​ ​​
​​​ ​I’ve completely lost the plot.​ ​​
​​​ ​We’re at the point where they broke your glasses.​ ​​
​​​ ​Stop this, both of you!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey you, tinheads, stop it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Fёdor is going to be back soon, and…​ ​​
​​​ ​ I’ll take you with my bare ha…​ ​​
​​​ ​nds!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, that’s exactly how it went. Thanks.​ ​​
​​​ ​Then you tell us, Kuromaku…​ ​​
​​​ ​[Co]oking [S]oup​ ​​
​​​ ​The situation is getting out of control.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yo, Mr Maku! It's easier to help the hungry than someone who’s had too large a B-BATCH of soup.​ ​​
​​​ ​What was he thinking about?​ ​​
​​​ ​How should I know? Ask him.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, yeah… Dante, what were you thinking?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah… I don’t remember.​ ​​
​​​ ​Dante! Watch the onions!​ ​​
​​​ ​I will saaave you!​ ​​
​​​ ​The crowd is not so much to dread, as the ringleader ahead…​ ​​
​​​ ​You have to be more careful!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh well. Are you hurt?​ ​​
​​​ ​This soup is too thick. We have to dilute it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you kindly, Dante.​ ​​
​​​ ​Now to add more salt.​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Vinegar?​ ​​
​​​ ​Soda…​ ​​
​​​ ​I’m angry, but I am impressed at your basic knowledge of chemistry.​ ​​
​​​ ​Who do you think I am?​ ​​
​​​ ​Grew old and bald, but wisdom never called.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well… Looks like the soup is ready…​ ​​
​​​ ​Who’s gonna try it?​ ​​
​​​ ​No...​ ​​
​​​ ​How so? You put so much effort in helping us cook.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, yeah! It’s just that I don’t like soups!​ ​​
​​​ ​I prefer beef patties​ ​​
​​​ ​with cheese-AHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​This… explains a lot.​ ​​
​​​ ​Guys, don’t worry.​ ​​
​​​ ​I’m feeling absolutely fine.​ ​​
​​​ ​Agh!… How creepy…​ ​​
​​​ ​You’ve dragged out the story…​ ​​
​​ ​Everything is much simpler!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let’s approach this a different way.​ ​​
​​​ ​What is soup? What does it mean?​ ​​
​​​ ​How did it come into our lives? Why is the author so focused on it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Why is the soup in the epicentre of the plot?​ ​​
​​​ ​What if soup is our life, and we’re merely ingredients within it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Don’t we cook every day in the feeling of detachment, as if we’re not in the recipe?​ ​​
​​​ ​Worrying at night, yearning for our place in the broth?​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe instead of spoiling in someone else’s plate we should find our own?​ ​​
​​​ ​But… Can the ingredients really decide where and how they are to be cooked?​ ​​
​​​ ​Who’s the cook?​ ​​
​​​ ​Whose soup is it?​ ​​
​​​ ​IT WAS MY SOUP!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah!​ ​​
​​​ ​I was just making soup, but when I stepped away…​ ​​
​​​ ​(Ominous laughter)​ ​​
​​​ ​Why didn’t you tell us?​ ​​
​​​ ​As if I could…​ ​​
​​​ ​Don’t worry, Brolly!​ ​​
​​​ ​We’ll help you make new soup.​ ​​
​​​ ​Only through mistakes does art gain strength.​ ​​
​​​ ​Destructive…​ ​​
​​​ ​Well… At least it’s not too salty…​ ​​
​​​ ​Sigh. Should we throw it?​ ​​
​​​ ​(all together) Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​I’m home, what have you… WHAT?!​ ​​
​​​ ​(Eve ryone) What?​ ​​
​​​ ​We made pasta!​ ​​
​​​ ​You want some?​ ​​
​​​ ​​​ ​​